{
    "subject": "Bert_Haanstra",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Alleman__film_",
    "human_readable": "Bert Haanstra directed the film Alleman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9030633568763733,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Bert Haanstra."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8832738399505615,
            "question": "Who directed the film Alleman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8455884456634521,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.765667200088501,
            "question": "Is Bert Haanstra a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6113041043281555,
            "question": "Who were some of the actors in the film Alleman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5945295691490173,
            "question": "Was Alleman a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5760210156440735,
            "question": "Where was the film Alleman filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5511186122894287,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film by Bert Haanstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5215339660644531,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film Alleman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3468951880931854,
            "question": "What type of work did Bert Haanstra create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bert Haanstra directed the film Alleman.",
            "html": "yago_11078_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of the film Alleman?",
            "html": "yago_11078_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a film by Bert Haanstra?",
            "html": "yago_11078_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film Alleman filmed?",
            "html": "yago_11078_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11078_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to be evaluated is:\n\n\"Bert Haanstra directed the film Alleman.\"\n\nGiven the context information and without prior knowledge, here's the evaluation:\n\n* The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11078/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt mentions \"Bert Haanstra\" as the director of the film \"Alleman\".\n* The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11078/re-ranker-msmarco/106.txt mentions \"Award-winning documentary in which Bert Haanstra portrays the Dutch population...\" and further mentions that the film was directed by Bert Haanstra.\n* The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11078/re-ranker-msmarco/103.txt is similar to the one at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_11078/re-ranker-msmarco/106.txt and also mentions that Bert Haanstra directed the film.\n\nTherefore, based on the provided context information, the evaluation is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Bert Haanstra directed the film Alleman.\" Specifically, document `44.txt` mentions \"Alleman : een film van Bert Haanstra,\" and other documents discuss his work on documentaries and films such as \"Jan en alleman.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}